{
    "name": ".\\Italian\\Gianliugi_Vocab.json",
    "vocab": [
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "riposarsi",
            "failed": 17,
            "lastAsked": 1492016934.7568262,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to relax\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 22
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "soltanto",
            "failed": 13,
            "lastAsked": 1492016845.4124544,
            "question": "Given the definition \"only\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 18
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "nascosto",
            "failed": 14,
            "lastAsked": 1492016928.3022282,
            "question": "Given the definition \"hidden\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 19
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "divertirsi",
            "failed": 13,
            "lastAsked": 1492016924.8620965,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to have fun\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 18
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "indimenticabile",
            "failed": 12,
            "lastAsked": 1492016916.4901965,
            "question": "Given the definition \"unforgettable\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 17
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "amazing",
            "failed": 9,
            "lastAsked": 1492016856.0521016,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"sorprendente\"?",
            "tried": 14
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "cruciverba"
            ],
            "answer": "il cruciverba",
            "failed": 9,
            "lastAsked": 1492016851.07636,
            "question": "Given the definition \"crossword puzzle\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 14
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "thin voice",
                "thin (voice)"
            ],
            "answer": "thin(voice)",
            "failed": 8,
            "lastAsked": 1492016842.0045462,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"sottile\"?",
            "tried": 13
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sottile",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1492016966.296501,
            "question": "Given the definition \"thin(voice)\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 12
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "gli abitanti",
            "failed": 8,
            "lastAsked": 1492017015.7189252,
            "question": "Given the definition \"residents, inhabitants\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 13
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to relax",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1492017679.44189,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"riposarsi\"?",
            "tried": 12
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il significato",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1492016993.8840067,
            "question": "Given the definition \"meaning\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 12
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "residents"
            ],
            "answer": "residents, inhabitants",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1492017676.870168,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"gli abitanti\"?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la macelleria",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1492017012.087469,
            "question": "Given the definition \"butcher shop\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "castano",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1492017689.5615292,
            "question": "Given the definition \"chestnut (color)\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 11
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "incredibile",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1492016982.8676658,
            "question": "Given the definition \"unbelievable\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sorprendente",
            "failed": 9,
            "lastAsked": 1492017864.627743,
            "question": "Given the definition \"amazing\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 14
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "di tanto in tanto",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1492017737.4402916,
            "question": "Given the definition \"once in a while\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 11
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "but"
            ],
            "answer": "but, however",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1492017840.4170306,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"pero\"?",
            "tried": 12
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "unforgettable",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1492017813.4480355,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"indimenticabile\"?",
            "tried": 11
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ritornare",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1492017824.510459,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to return\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 11
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "hidden",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1492017807.9024105,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"nascosto\"?",
            "tried": 11
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "stare",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1492017820.8773947,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be, stay\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "piacevole",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1492017852.772689,
            "question": "Given the definition \"pleasant, enjoyable\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 11
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "unbelievable",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1492017966.0770123,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"incredibile\"?",
            "tried": 11
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "l'anno scorso",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1492017950.0454755,
            "question": "Given the definition \"last year\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "fare quattro chicchiere",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1492017987.272966,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to chat\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 11
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "inventare",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1492017933.562146,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to invent\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "raccontare",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1492017919.1911402,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to tell stories\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to be born",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1492017922.882357,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"nascere\"?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "tranquillo",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1492017938.3462994,
            "question": "Given the definition \"calm, quiet, tranquil\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "from time to time"
            ],
            "answer": "once in a while",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1492017894.7599854,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"di tanto in tanto\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "nemmeno",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1492018075.4100993,
            "question": "Given the definition \"not even\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "stay, period of time"
            ],
            "answer": "stay, duration",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1492018073.0699344,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il soggiorno\"?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "voce"
            ],
            "answer": "la voce",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1492018067.833945,
            "question": "Given the definition \"voice\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "chestnut",
                "chestnut color"
            ],
            "answer": "chestnut (color)",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1492017993.8162808,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"castano\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "smiling",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1492018039.9417944,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"sorridente\"?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "andare a trovare",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1492018055.689822,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to visit someone\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "only",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1492018042.4544475,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"soltanto\"?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "straordinario",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1492018045.5505562,
            "question": "Given the definition \"extraordinary\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "nephew or grandson"
            ],
            "answer": "nephew, grandson",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1492018146.235466,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il nipote\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "l'eta",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1492018119.1124966,
            "question": "Given the definition \"age\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "paese",
                "il paese"
            ],
            "answer": "il pasese",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1492018168.3585012,
            "question": "Given the definition \"town\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "faccia"
            ],
            "answer": "la faccia",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1492018157.8072634,
            "question": "Given the definition \"face\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il soggiorno",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492018089.7490916,
            "question": "Given the definition \"stay, duration\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "gli occhi",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1492018154.5917096,
            "question": "Given the definition \"eyes\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "while",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1492018163.9507606,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"mentre\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to visit someone",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492018101.5328991,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"andare a trovare\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "provencia",
                "provincia"
            ],
            "answer": "la provincia",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1492018240.2722719,
            "question": "Given the definition \"province\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "avere",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1492018232.2364266,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to have\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "dove'"
            ],
            "answer": "dove",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1492018247.2282608,
            "question": "Given the definition \"where\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "lavorare",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1492018218.4447632,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to work\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vivere",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1492018242.7125056,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to live\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "fast",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1492018220.740671,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"veloce\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to invent",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492018171.2384517,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"inventare\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "butcher shop",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1492018224.628673,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la macelleria\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to listen to someone"
            ],
            "answer": "to listen to",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1492018390.4082382,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ascoltare\"?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the town"
            ],
            "answer": "town",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492018287.855182,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il pasese\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to know someone"
            ],
            "answer": "to know a person",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1492018379.9279962,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"conoscere\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "grasso",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1492018294.102747,
            "question": "Given the definition \"chubby, fat\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "not even",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1492018382.5356953,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"nemmeno\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "curioso",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1492018291.6460848,
            "question": "Given the definition \"curious\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "secondo me",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492018251.0202742,
            "question": "Given the definition \"in my opinion\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "ragazzino"
            ],
            "answer": "il ragazzino",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1492018387.7521102,
            "question": "Given the definition \"a little boy\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sorridente",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492018689.862404,
            "question": "Given the definition \"smiling\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "pero",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1492018794.1511545,
            "question": "Given the definition \"but, however\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "relatives",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492018723.7934563,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"i parenti\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "mentre",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492018787.1752763,
            "question": "Given the definition \"while\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "pleasant"
            ],
            "answer": "pleasant, enjoyable",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492018801.1346507,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"piacevole\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "infatti",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1492018803.2589595,
            "question": "Given the definition \"in fact\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "perche"
            ],
            "answer": "perche'",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492018790.495479,
            "question": "Given the definition \"because\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "crossword puzzle",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492018798.2069268,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il cruciverba\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "in fact",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492018814.8783123,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"infatti\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "forte",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1492018842.2896323,
            "question": "Given the definition \"strong\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "astuto",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1492018839.7620301,
            "question": "Given the definition \"astute, clever\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "un po'",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492018829.7017097,
            "question": "Given the definition \"a bit\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "age",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492018816.9662817,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"l'eta\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "fare",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492018808.1948721,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to do, make\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to tell a story"
            ],
            "answer": "to tell stories",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492018812.830618,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"raccontare\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vedere",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492018823.2699938,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to see\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the face"
            ],
            "answer": "face",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492018854.0172465,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la faccia\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "nascere",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492018874.928562,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be born\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ascoltare",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492018860.893419,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to listen to\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "piacere",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492018878.1121562,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to like\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "extraordinary",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492018847.1131434,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"straordinario\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to have a chat"
            ],
            "answer": "to chat",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492018871.9770503,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"fare quattro chicchiere\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "i parenti",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492018851.8527415,
            "question": "Given the definition \"relatives\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "tranquil",
                "tranquil, peaceful"
            ],
            "answer": "calm, quiet, tranquil",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492018858.0290272,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"tranquillo\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "capelli",
                "cappelli"
            ],
            "answer": "i capelli",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492018920.4555001,
            "question": "Given the definition \"hair\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "big"
            ],
            "answer": "large, big",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492018896.6556582,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"grande\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "little"
            ],
            "answer": "small",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492018889.9203036,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"piccolo\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "in my opinion",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492018886.0964193,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"secondo me\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "alto",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492018913.6273909,
            "question": "Given the definition \"tall, high\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "a place",
                "the place"
            ],
            "answer": "place",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492018906.4835575,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il posto\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "fat, chubby",
                "fat"
            ],
            "answer": "chubby, fat",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492018887.9362662,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"grasso\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "conoscere",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492018894.7758114,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to know a person\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "small boy",
                "the little boy"
            ],
            "answer": "a little boy",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492018923.8148959,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il ragazzino\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to like",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492018945.9419913,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"piacere\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the voice"
            ],
            "answer": "voice",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492018925.9753225,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la voce\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to have",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492018943.2859766,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"avere\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "where",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492018930.0306048,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"dove\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to see",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492018941.3105001,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"vedere\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to watch"
            ],
            "answer": "to look at, watch",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492018928.3427958,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"guardare\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to stay"
            ],
            "answer": "to be, stay",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492019052.291168,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"stare\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "hair",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492019069.6386132,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"i capelli\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "strong",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492019065.1831963,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"forte\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "nipote"
            ],
            "answer": "il nipote",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492019077.7424796,
            "question": "Given the definition \"nephew, grandson\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to be",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492019063.3384805,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"essere\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "parlare",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492019094.961559,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to speak, talk\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "essere",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492019100.345499,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to have fun",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492019060.099096,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"divertirsi\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to return",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492019067.7986236,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ritornare\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "guardare",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492019118.8764982,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to look at, watch\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "a little"
            ],
            "answer": "a bit",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492019115.5213356,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"un po'\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to work",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492019102.9055605,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"lavorare\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "tall"
            ],
            "answer": "tall, high",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492019124.6684713,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"alto\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "domanda"
            ],
            "answer": "la domanda",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492019127.3887312,
            "question": "Given the definition \"question\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "grande",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492019109.1127384,
            "question": "Given the definition \"large, big\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "why, because",
                "why"
            ],
            "answer": "because",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492019122.308853,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"perche'\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to speak"
            ],
            "answer": "to speak, talk",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492019105.3134105,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"parlare\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the province"
            ],
            "answer": "province",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492019137.4761033,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la provincia\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "curious",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492019150.8964736,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"curioso\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "summer",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492019160.7758715,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"l'estate\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the eyes"
            ],
            "answer": "eyes",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492019141.8802364,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"gli occhi\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to do"
            ],
            "answer": "to do, make",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492019145.2637744,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"fare\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "astute",
                "smart",
                "astute, smart"
            ],
            "answer": "astute, clever",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492019148.8721054,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"astuto\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "piccolo",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492019159.5274014,
            "question": "Given the definition \"small\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the question"
            ],
            "answer": "question",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492019139.588284,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la domanda\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to live",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492019175.5231552,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"vivere\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "veloce",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492019167.0474381,
            "question": "Given the definition \"fast\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the year before"
            ],
            "answer": "last year",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492019179.3875546,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"l'anno scorso\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "l'estate",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492019173.4516156,
            "question": "Given the definition \"summer\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "meaning",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492019164.2313526,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il significato\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il posto",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492019182.3262463,
            "question": "Given the definition \"place\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        }
    ]
}